

CONTACT

- +65 93547819
- ✓ teckhong0817@gmail.com
- 49# 12 120, Dorset RD, Singapore 210049

EDUCATION

2016 - 2021 SMK KELAPA SAWIT

· Secondary School

2023 - CURRENT REPUBLIC POLYTECHNIC

 Diploma in Digital Design and Development

SKILLS

- Python
- JavaScript
- CSS
- HTML
- Unity
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop

LANGUAGES

- English
- Chinese
- Malay

PANG TECK HONG

DIPLOMA STUDENT IN REPUBLIC POLYTECHNIC

PROFILE

I am currently a Republic Polytechnic student for a diploma in Digital Design and Development. I have skill in UI/UX design and web development, and I also have knowledge in Bootstrap 5, JavaScript, HTML, and CSS. I always strive for my project to be an enjoyable experience for user, and create something that I will be proud of in the end of the day.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Wingstop

Part-Time Kitchen Crew

2024 - CURRENT

- · Making and preparing fried chicken.
- · Maintain restaurant's cleanliness.

Haidilao Hot Pot

2023 - 2024

Part-Time Service Crew

- Serving customers, satisfy customer's needs, and helping customer proceed to payment.
- · Maintain restaurant's cleanliness.

Ganko Sushi

2022 - 2023

Full Time Service Crew

- Taking customer order, assist customer for dining.
- Clear table and maintain restaurant's cleanliness.